A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1947-1951 FA759
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1948
  - Venezuela - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/339.E
    - Venezuela - (A-B), 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2829)
    - Venezuela, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2830)
  - Venezuela - Public Health Education, 1948; 02.1948/339.L
    - Venezuela, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2830)
  - Great Britain, 1948; 02.1948/400
    - Great Britain, 1948 (Box 420, Folder 2831)
  - England, 1948; 02.1948/401
    - England (A-G), 1948 (Box 420, Folder 2832)
    - England (H-M), 1948 (Box 420, Folder 2833)
    - England (N-O), 1948 (Box 420, Folder 2834)
    - England (P-R), 1948 (Box 420, Folder 2835)
    - England (S-Z), 1948 (Box 420, Folder 2836)
  - England - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/401.A
    - England, 1948 (Box 420, Folder 2837)
  - England - Social Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/401.S
    - England, 1948 (Box 420, Folder 2837)
  - Ireland, 1948; 02.1948/403
    - Ireland, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2838)
  - Ireland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/403.E
    - Ireland, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2838)
  - Scotland, 1948; 02.1948/405
    - Scotland, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2838)
  - Scotland - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 02.1948/405.D
    - Scotland, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2838)
  - Scotland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/405.E
    - Scotland, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2838)
  - Wales, 1948; 02.1948/407
    - Wales, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2838)
  - Australia, 1948; 02.1948/410
    - Australia, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2839)
  - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/410.A
    - Australia, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2839)
  - Australia - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/410.C
    - Australia, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2839)
  - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/410.E
    - Australia, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2839)
  - Australia - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/410.R
    - Australia, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2839)
  - Tasmania, 1948; 02.1948/414
    - Sydenham Hospital, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2840)
  - New Zealand, 1948; 02.1948/418
    - New Zealand, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2840)
  - New Zealand - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/418.A
    - New Zealand, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2840)
  - New Zealand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/418.E
    - New Zealand, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2840)
  - New Zealand - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/418.R
    - New Zealand, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2840)
  - Caribbean, 1948; 02.1948/420
    - Caribbean Region - Administration, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2841)
    - Caribbean Region - Administration, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2842)
    - Caribbean Region - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2843)
  - Guyana, 1948; 02.1948/423
    - Guiana, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2843)
  - Canada, 1948; 02.1948/427
    - Canada - Administration, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2844)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2845)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2846)
  - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/427.A
    - Canada, 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2847)
  - Canada - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/427.C
    - Canada, 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2847)
  - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/427.E
    - Canada, 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2847)
  - Canada, 1948; 02.1948/427.R
    - Canada, 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2848)
  - Jamaica, 1948; 02.1948/437
    - Jamaica, 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2849)
  - Trinidad, 1948; 02.1948/451
    - Trinidad, 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2849)
  - Grenada, 1948; 02.1948/455
    - Grenada, 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2849)
  - India, 1948; 02.1948/464
    - India - General Administration - (A-D), 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2850)
    - India - (E-Z), 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2851)
  - India - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/464.A
    - India, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2852)
  - India - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/464.C
    - India, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2852)
  - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/464.E
    - India, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2852)
  - India - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/464.R
    - India, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2852)
  - India - Social Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/464.S
    - India, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2852)
  - Pakistan, 1948; 02.1948/465
    - Pakistan, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Pakistan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/465.E
    - Pakistan, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Pakistan - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/465.R
    - Pakistan, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Burma, 1948; 02.1948/468
    - Burma, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Burma - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/468.A
    - Burma, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Burma - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/468.R
    - Burma, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Iraq, 1948; 02.1948/470
    - Iraq, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Singapore, 1948; 02.1948/473
    - Singapore, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Africa, 1948; 02.1948/475
    - Africa, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Africa - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/475.R
    - Africa, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Kenya, 1948; 02.1948/476
    - East Africa, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Ethiopia, 1948; 02.1948/477
    - Ethiopia, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Rhodesia, 1948; 02.1948/483
    - Zimbabwe - Rhodesia, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Egypt, 1948; 02.1948/485
    - Egypt - Administration, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2854)
    - Egypt - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2855)
  - Egypt - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/485.C
    - Egypt, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2856)
  - Egypt - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/485.E
    - Egypt, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2856)
  - South Africa, 1948; 02.1948/487
    - South Africa, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2857)
  - South Africa - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/487.A
    - South Africa, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2857)
  - South Africa - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/487.E
    - South Africa, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2857)
  - South Africa - Yellow Fever, 1948; 02.1948/487.O
    - South Africa, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2857)
  - Zaire, 1948; 02.1948/495
    - Zaire, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2857)
  - France, 1948; 02.1948/500
    - France - (A-G), 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2858)
    - France - (H-N), 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2859)
    - France - (O-Z), 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2860)
  - France - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/500.A
    - France, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2861)
  - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/500.E
    - France, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2861)
  - France - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/500.R
    - France, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2861)
  - France - Social Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/500.S
    - France, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2861)
  - French West Africa, 1948; 02.1948/521
    - French Africa, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2862)
  - Asia, 1948; 02.1948/600
    - Asia, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2862)
  - Asia - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/600.R
    - Asia, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2862)
  - China, 1948; 02.1948/601
    - China - Administration, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2863)
    - China - Administration, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2864)
    - China - (A-P), 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2865)
    - China - (A-P), 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2866)
    - China - (S-Z), 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2867)
  - China - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/601.A
    - China, 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2868)
  - China - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/601.C
    - China, 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2868)
  - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/601.E
  - China, 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2868)
  - China - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/601.R
    - China, 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2868)
  - China - Social Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/601.S
    - China, 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2868)
  - Taiwan, 1948; 02.1948/605
  - Taiwan - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/605.A
    - Taiwan, 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2869)
  - Taiwan - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/605.C
    - Taiwan, 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2869)
  - Taiwan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/605.E
    - Taiwan, 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2869)
  - Japan, 1948; 02.1948/609
    - Japan - (General) - (A-I), 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2870)
    - Japan - (J-N), 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2871)
    - Japan - (O-Z), 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2872)
  - Japan - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/609.A
    - Japan, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2872)
  - Japan - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/609.C
    - Japan, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2872)
  - Japan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 02.1948/609.D
    - Japan, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2872)
  - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/609.E
    - Japan - (O-Z), 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2872)
    - Japan, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2872)
  - Japan - Social Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/609.S
    - Japan, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2872)
    - Japan, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2872)
  - Korea, 1948; 02.1948/613
    - Korea, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2873)
  - Korea - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/613.A
    - Korea, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2873)
  - Korea - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/613.C
    - Korea, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2873)
  - Korea - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/613.R
    - Korea, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2873)
  - Thailand, 1948; 02.1948/617
    - Thailand, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2873)
  - Holland, 1948; 02.1948/650
    - Holland - (A-T), 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2874)
    - Holland - (U-Z), 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2875)
  - Holland - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/650.A
    - Holland - (U-Z), 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2875)
  - Holland - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 02.1948/650.D
    - Holland, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2875)
  - Holland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/650.E
    - Holland, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2875)
  - Holland - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/650.R
    - Holland, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2875)
  - Indonesia, 1948; 02.1948/652
    - Indonesia, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2876)
  - Indonesia - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/652.R
    - Indonesia, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2876)
  - Pontianak, 1948; 02.1948/653
    - Pontianak, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2876)
  - Dutch East Indies, 1948; 02.1948/654
    - Dutch East Indies, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2876)
  - Java, 1948; 02.1948/655
    - Java, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2876)
  - Europe, 1948; 02.1948/700
    - Europe - Rehabilitation Programs, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2877)
    - Europe - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2878)
  - Europe - Social Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/700.S
    - Europe, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2878)
  - Afghanistan, 1948; 02.1948/703
  - Afghanistan - Malaria, 1948; 02.1948/703.I
    - Afghanistan, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2879)
  - Albania, 1948; 02.1948/704
    - Albania, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2879)
  - Austria, 1948; 02.1948/705
    - Austria, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2879)
    - Austria - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2880)
  - Austria - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/705.A
    - Austria, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2880)
  - Austria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/705.E
    - Austria, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2880)
  - Austria - Tuberculosis, 1948; 02.1948/705.T
    - Austria, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2880)
  - Belgium, 1948; 02.1948/707
    - Belgium, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2881)
  - Belgium - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/707.A
    - Belgium, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2881)
  - Belgium - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/707.E
    - Belgium, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2881)
  - Belgium - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/707.R
    - Belgium, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2881)
  - Zaire, 1948; 02.1948/709
    - Zaire, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2882)
  - Yugoslavia, 1948; 02.1948/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2882)
  - Yugoslavia - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/710.A
    - Yugoslavia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2882)
  - Yugoslavia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 02.1948/710.D
    - Yugoslavia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2882)
  - Bulgaria, 1948; 02.1948/711
    - Bulgaria, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2882)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1948; 02.1948/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2882)
  - Czechoslovakia - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/712.A
    - Czechoslovakia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
  - Czechoslovakia - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/712.C
    - Czechoslovakia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
  - Czechoslovakia - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/712.C
    - Czechoslovakia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
  - Czechoslovakia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/712.E
    - Czechoslovakia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
  - Denmark, 1948; 02.1948/713
    - Denmark, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
  - Denmark - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/713.A
    - Denmark, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
  - Denmark - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 02.1948/713.D
    - Denmark, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
  - Denmark - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/713.E
    - Denmark, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
  - Denmark - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/713.R
    - Denmark, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
  - Scandinavia, 1948; 02.1948/716
    - Scandinavia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
  - Germany, 1948; 02.1948/717
    - Germany - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 428, Folder 2884)
    - Germany - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 428, Folder 2885)
    - Germany - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 428, Folder 2886)
  - Germany - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/717.A
    - Germany, 1948 (Box 428, Folder 2887)
  - Germany - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 02.1948/717.D
    - Germany, 1948 (Box 428, Folder 2887)
  - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/717.E
    - Germany, 1948 (Box 428, Folder 2888)
  - Germany - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/717.R
    - Germany, 1948 (Box 428, Folder 2888)
  - Germany - Social Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/717.S
    - Germany, 1948 (Box 428, Folder 2888)
  - Greece, 1948; 02.1948/749
    - Greece, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2889)
  - Greece - Malaria, 1948; 02.1948/749.I
    - Greece, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2889)
  - Hungary, 1948; 02.1948/750
    - Hungary, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2889)
    - Hungary - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2890)
  - Hungary - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/750.A
    - Hungary, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2891)
  - Hungary - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/750.E
    - Hungary, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2891)
  - Hungary - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/750.R
    - Hungary, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2891)
  - Italy, 1948; 02.1948/751
    - Italy - (A-R), 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2892)
    - Italy - (S-Z), 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2893)
  - Italy - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/751.A
    - Italy - (S-Z), 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2893)
  - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/751.E
    - Italy - (S-Z), 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2893)
  - Italy - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/751.R
    - Italy - (S-Z), 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2893)
  - Italy - Social Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/751.S
    - Italy - (S-Z), 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2893)
  - Luxembourg, 1948; 02.1948/760
    - Luxembourg, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2894)
  - Norway, 1948; 02.1948/767
    - Norway, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2894)
  - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/767.E
    - Norway, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2894)
  - Norway - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/767.R
    - Norway, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2894)
  - Iran, 1948; 02.1948/771
    - Iran, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2895)
  - Iran - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/771.C
    - Iran, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2896)
  - Iran - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/771.E
    - Iran, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2896)
  - Iran - Malaria, 1948; 02.1948/771.I
    - Iran, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2896)
  - Iran - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/771.R
    - Iran, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2896)
  - Portugal, 1948; 02.1948/773
    - Portugal, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - Portugal - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/773.C
    - Portugal, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - Portugal - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 02.1948/773.D
    - Portugal, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - Portugal - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/773.E
    - Portugal, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - Portugal - Malaria, 1948; 02.1948/773.I
    - Portugal, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - Portugal - Romania, 1948; 02.1948/783
    - Romania, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - Ukraine, 1948; 02.1948/784
  - Ukraine - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/784.A
    - Ukraine, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - USSR, 1948; 02.1948/785
    - USSR, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - USSR - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 02.1948/785.D
    - USSR, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - USSR - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/785.R
    - USSR, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - USSR - Social Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/785.S
    - USSR, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - Latvia, 1948; 02.1948/786
    - Latvia, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - Finland, 1948; 02.1948/787
    - Finland, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2898)
  - Finland - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/787.A
    - Finland, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2898)
  - Finland - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 02.1948/787.D
    - Finland, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2898)
  - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/787.E
    - Finland, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2898)
  - Poland, 1948; 02.1948/789
    - Poland, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2898)
  - Poland - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/789.A
    - Poland, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2898)
  - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/789.E
    - Poland, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2898)
  - Poland - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/789.R
    - Poland, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2898)
  - Spain, 1948; 02.1948/795
    - Spain, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2899)
  - Sweden, 1948; 02.1948/800
    - Sweden, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2899)
  - Sweden - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/800.A
    - Sweden, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2899)
  - Sweden - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/800.C
    - Sweden, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2899)
  - Sweden - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 02.1948/800.D
    - Sweden, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2899)
  - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/800.E
    - Sweden, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2899)
  - Sweden - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/800.R
    - Sweden, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2899)
  - Liechtenstein, 1948; 02.1948/802
  - Liechtenstein - Malaria, 1948; 02.1948/802.I
    - Liechtenstein, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2900)
  - Switzerland, 1948; 02.1948/803
    - Switzerland, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2900)
  - Switzerland - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/803.A
    - Switzerland, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2900)
  - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/803.E
    - Switzerland, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2900)
  - Switzerland - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/803.R
    - Switzerland, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2900)
  - Near East Region, 1948; 02.1948/804
  - Near East Region - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/804.R
    - Middle East, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2901)
    - MAR-1 Marshall, John "Middle East Trip", 1948 (Box 563, Folder 3837)
  - Turkey, 1948; 02.1948/805
    - Turkey, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2901)
  - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/805.E
    - Turkey, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2901)
  - Turkey - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/805.R
    - Turkey, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2901)
  - Turkey - Social Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/805.S
    - Turkey, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2901)
  - Crete, 1948; 02.1948/807
    - Crete, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2901)
  - Cyprus, 1948; 02.1948/809
    - Cyprus, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2901)
  - Saudi Arabia and Oman, 1948; 02.1948/817
    - Saudi Arabia, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2901)
  - Israel, 1948; 02.1948/825
    - Israel, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2902)
  - Israel - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/825.A
    - Israel, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2902)
  - Lebanon, 1948; 02.1948/833
    - Syria/Lebanon, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2902)
  - Lebanon - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/833.C
    - Syria/Lebanon, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2902)
  - Lebanon - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/833.R
    - Syria/Lebanon, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2902)
- General Correspondence, 1949
  - International, 1949; 02.1949/100
    - Staff - International - Aitken, Thomas H., 1949 (Box 431, Folder 2903)
    - Staff - International - Anderson, Richard K., 1949 (Box 431, Folder 2904)
    - Staff - International - Balfour, M. C., 1949 (Box 431, Folder 2905)
    - Staff - International - Bates, Marston, 1949 (Box 431, Folder 2906)
    - Staff - International - Belknap, Chauncey - Bevier, George, 1949 (Box 432, Folder 2907)
    - Staff - International - Buchanan, Norman S. - Bugher, John C. - Burden, Robert P., 1949 (Box 432, Folder 2908)
    - Staff - International - Carr, Henry P., 1949 (Box 432, Folder 2909)
    - Staff - International - Carter, J. C. - Causey, O. R., 1949 (Box 432, Folder 2910)
    - Staff - International - Classification of Knowledge - (Articles), 1949 (Box 432, Folder 2911)
    - Staff - International - Copley, Cecil G. - Crowell, F. Elisabeth - Debevoise, Thomas M. - Diplomatic Service, 1949 (Box 432, Folder 2912)
    - Staff - International - Dyer, Brian R., 1949 (Box 433, Folder 2913)
    - Staff - International - Elmendorf, John E., 1949 (Box 433, Folder 2914)
    - Staff - International - Fahs, Charles B. - Fox, John P., 1949 (Box 433, Folder 2915)
    - Staff - International - Grant, John B. - Gregg, Alan, 1949 (Box 433, Folder 2916)
    - Staff - International - Hackett, Lewis W., 1949 (Box 433, Folder 2917)
    - Staff - International - Hackett, Lewis W., 1949 (Box 433, Folder 2918)
    - Staff - International - Hahn, Richard G., 1949 (Box 434, Folder 2919)
    - Staff - International - Hayes, Guy S., 1949 (Box 434, Folder 2920)
    - Staff - International - Hill, Rolla B. - Hirst, Esther Mary - Hughes, Thomas P., 1949 (Box 434, Folder 2921)
    - Staff - International - Information Exchange - Institute of Current World Affairs, 1949 (Box 434, Folder 2922)
    - Staff - International - International - (A-Z), 1949 (Box 434, Folder 2923)
    - Staff - International - Janney, John H., 1949 (Box 434, Folder 2924)
    - Staff - International - Kendrick, John F. - Kerr, J. Austin - Kimball, Lindsley F., 1949 (Box 435, Folder 2925)
    - Staff - International - Kitchen, Stuart F., 1949 (Box 435, Folder 2926)
    - Staff - International - Lambert, Robert A., 1949 (Box 435, Folder 2927)
    - Staff - International - Leach, Charles L., 1949 (Box 435, Folder 2928)
    - Staff - International - Logan, John A., 1949 (Box 435, Folder 2929)
    - Staff - International - McCoy, O. R., 1949 (Box 435, Folder 2930)
    - Staff - International - Magoon, Estus H. - Mailing Lists, 1949 (Box 435, Folder 2931)
    - Staff - International - Maier, John, 1949 (Box 435, Folder 2932)
    - Staff - International - Marshall, John - Milam, D. Frank, 1949 (Box 436, Folder 2933)
    - Staff - International - Miller, Harry M. - Morison, Robert S., 1949 (Box 436, Folder 2934)
    - Staff - International - Noll, Anna Mary - Oliver, Wale, 1949 (Box 436, Folder 2935)
    - Staff - International - Pan-American Institute of Geography and History, 1949 (Box 436, Folder 2936)
    - Staff - International - Paul, J. Harland, 1949 (Box 436, Folder 2937)
    - Staff - International - Payne, George C. - Peterson, Osler L., 1949 (Box 436, Folder 2938)
    - Staff - International - Pomerat, Gerard R. - Rhind, Flora M. - Rickard, E. R. - Russell, Paul F., 1949 (Box 436, Folder 2939)
    - Staff - International - Sasse, Bruce E. - Smith, H. H. - Smithburn, Kenneth, 1949 (Box 437, Folder 2940)
    - Staff - International - Stevens, David H., 1949 (Box 437, Folder 2941)
    - Staff - International - Strode, George K., 1949 (Box 437, Folder 2942)
    - Staff - International - Taylor, R. M., 1949 (Box 437, Folder 2943)
    - Staff - International - Tennant, Mary Elizabeth, 1949 (Box 437, Folder 2944)